const STORE = [
  {
    questionNumber: 1,
    question: 'What position does Harry play on his Quidditch team?',
    answer1: 'Chaser',
    answer2: 'Seeker',
    answer3: 'Bludger',
    answer4: 'Keeper',
    correctAnswer: 'Seeker'
  },
  {
    questionNumber: 2,
    question: 'Name the centaur who taught at Hogwarts.',
    answer1: 'Professor Dumbledore',
    answer2: 'James Potter',
    answer3: 'Professor Firenze',
    answer4: 'Professor McGonagall',
    correctAnswer: 'Professor Firenze'
  },
  {
    questionNumber: 3,
    question: 'Cedric Diggory faced what breed of dragon in the Triwizard Tournament?',
    answer1: 'Swedish Short-Snout',
    answer2: 'Peruvian Vipertooth',
    answer3: 'Norwegian Ridgeback',
    answer4: 'Common Welsh Green',
    correctAnswer: 'Swedish Short-Snout'
  },
  {
    questionNumber: 4,
    question:
      'What animal represents Hufflepuff house?',
    answer1: 'Lion',
    answer2: 'Eagle',
    answer3: 'Badger',
    answer4: 'Serpent',
    correctAnswer: 'Badger'
  },
  {
    questionNumber: 5,
    question: 'Where did Harry and Ron crash the Ford Anglia?',
    answer1: 'Hogwarts',
    answer2: 'Whomping Willow',
    answer3: 'Forbidden Forest',
    answer4: 'Hogsmeade',
    correctAnswer: 'Whomping Willow'
  },
  {
    questionNumber: 6,
    question:
      'In the Hall of Prophecy there are rows and rows of glowing orbs. Which row contains the prophecy about Harry and Voldemort?',
    answer1: "Row 97",
    answer2: 'Row 20',
    answer3: 'Row 74',
    answer4: 'Row 89',
    correctAnswer: 'Row 97'
  },
  {
    questionNumber: 7,
    question:
      'Which character served as a Quidditch commentator?',
    answer1: 'Lee Jordan' , 
    answer2: 'George Weasley',
    answer3: ' Ron Weasley',
    answer4: 'Oliver Wood',
    correctAnswer: 'Lee Jordan'
  },
  {
    questionNumber: 8,
    question:
      'Luna tells Harry ‘things we lose have a way of coming back to us in the end. If not always in the ways we expect’ but who used to say this to Luna?',
    answer1: 'Her Mum',
    answer2: 'Nargles',
    answer3: 'Her Dad',
    answer4: 'Her Grandmother',
    correctAnswer: 'Her Mum'
  },
  {
    questionNumber: 9,
    question:
      'Gilderoy Lockhart tried to use ‘Brackium Emendo’ to fix Harry’s broken bones. What did it actually do to him?', 
    answer1: 'Turned his leg wooden',
    answer2:' Removed his bones entirely',
    answer3: 'Forced him to speak Parseltongue',
    answer4: 'Gave him an exquisite singing voice',
    correctAnswer: ' Removed his bones entirely'
  },
  {
    questionNumber: 10,
    question:
      'How many staircases does Hogwarts have?',
    answer1: "149",
    answer2: '264',
    answer3: '387',
    answer4: '142',
    correctAnswer: '142'
  }
];
